《边桥谜案》前情提要
Previously on the Bridge...
我们去哪
Where are we going?
有人吗  有人吗
Hello? Hello?
-格斯还活着  -何以见得
- Gus is alive. - Why do you say that?
他想让马可痛苦
He wants Marco to suffer.
如果有人抓了你儿子你会怎样
What would you do if someone had your son?
丹尼尔・弗莱失踪了  丹尼尔帮忙包庇了那场肇事逃逸
Daniel Frye is missing. Daniel helped cover up the hit-and-run.
就是戴维・泰特家的那场事故
David Tate's family.
他说正因为这样凶手才一直针对他
He told me that's why he's been targeted all this time.
离他远点  只管冲着我来
Leave him alone. Take it out on me.
我不是正在这么做吗  你一个人来
Well, isn't that what I'm doing? Come alone.
绝对不要带上她
Entirely alone, leave her.
别告诉任何人我去哪了
Don't tell anyone where I went.
-马可在哪  -他接了个电话就走了
- Hey, where's Marco? - He got a call and left.
谁打给他的
Got a call from who?
带枪了吗
You have a gun?
-带了  -很好  我来开车
- Yes. - Good. I'll drive.
杀了他
Shoot him.
我以为你只是想吓吓他
Thought you said we were gonna scare him.
我改主意了
Well, I changed my mind.
不要啊  不要
Ah! No, whoa, whoa whoa, whoa, whoa..
你身上的味道可不好闻  小蒂
You ain't smelling too good there, Timbo.
有人吗  你好
Hello. Hola.
这里有人吗
Anyone around?
天啊
Oh man!
该死
Oh, shit holy shit!
搞什么
What the hell?
冷静点  哥们  冷静点
Stay cool, bro stay cool, bro, stay cool.
我只是打算借这把佩德罗
I'm just gonna borrow this pedro.
搞什...
What the...?
放松点  蒂姆  要么干脆完全放松吧
Take it easy, Tim. Or don't take it at all.
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译
冰蓝
圈圈
爱卿遛小鸟
翻译
胖兔纯
蓬蓬裙
No.Zero
foolyangyang
校对
面条打包子
wdjmhs
时间轴
萌
imok
No.Zero
后期  吉吉
总监  wdjmhs
边桥谜案
第一季   第十一集
对于我妻子而言  痛苦是短暂的
For my wife, it was instant.
我知道你在想什么  别这样
I know what you're thinking. Don't.
我只希望儿子能活过来
I just want my son back.
车祸发生后  我儿子还活了十分钟
My son lived for ten minutes after the crash.
他叫迦勒  你记得吗
His name was Caleb, do you remember that?
很遗憾  戴维  很遗憾你失去了儿子
I'm sorry, David. I'm sorry you lost your son.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我能想象到他被压在车下  无法呼吸
I imagine him there. Under the car. Crushed. Unable to breathe.
-别说了  戴维  -我一直希望他那时
- Please, David. - I always hoped he was already gone, you know.
已经神游天外了  想着美好
In his head. Daydreaming about something nice.
温暖安全的事
Something warm and safe.
但我有种感觉  我深深地觉得
But I have a feeling, down in the utter bottom of myself,
对他来说并不是那样
that it wasn't like that for him.
我认为他孤独地死在一个寒冷黑暗的地方
I think it was like dying in a cold, dark place alone.
等着我去救他
Waiting for me to save him.
这是场意外  戴维
It was an accident, David.
但我没露面  他独自一人死去
But I never showed up, he died alone.
大概就在这里
Right about here, in fact.
-你在干什么  -下车吧
- What are you doing? - Here we go.
你干什么  戴维
What are you doing, David?
准备好了吗  马可
You ready, Marco?
退后  全都退后
Get back! Go back! Back! Everybody back!
这人身上有炸弹  都退后
Tiene una bomba! He's got a bomb! Back!
把边桥炸了也于事无补
Blowing up the bridge won't solve anything.
-那要看了  -看什么
- Well, it depends. - On what?
你还想见你儿子  对吧
You still want to see your son, right?
我要听你说  马可
I need to hear you say it, Marco.
是的  我想见儿子
Yes. I want to see my son.
那就开始吧  把后备箱打开
Then let's get started. Open the trunk.
弗莱
Frye.
让他出来
Get him out.
你怎么来了  你该在医院的
You shouldn't be here. You should be at the hospital.
我得找到格斯
I need to find Gus.
马可现在跟泰特在一起  是吧
So, Marco's with Tate, isn't he?
回答我  桑娅
Answer me, Sonya.
是的  他去见他了
Yes. He went to meet him.
所以你决定瞒着我
So you decide not to tell me.
事实上  你骗了我
In fact, you lied to me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
-桑娅  怎么了  -我也许知道他在哪
- Sonya, what is it? - I think I know where he is.
我得回沃尔特・钱伯斯家一趟
I have to go back to Walter Chambers' house.
桑娅  我们都查过了  什么都没有
Sonya, we've been all over that. There ain't nothin' there.
-我知道  我们遗漏了一些线索  -什么线索
- I know, but we're missing something. - Well, what'd we miss?
那个狗娘养的在美国境内的边桥上挟持着马可
That son of a bitch has Marco on the Bridge of the Americas.
他身上绑着炸弹
And he's got a bomb.
-格斯在吗  -不在  但丹尼尔・弗莱在
- Is Gus with them? - No, but Daniel Frye is.
-他会杀了他俩的  -不  这不符合他的复仇大计
- He's gonna kill them both. - No, it doesn't fit.
格斯也是其中的一部分
Gus is part of this, too
-我要去钱伯斯家  -库珀  跟她一起去
- I'm going to Chambers' house. - Cooper, go with her.
-我去边桥  有发现打我电话  -是  长官
- I'll be at the bridge. Call me if you find anything. - Yes, sir.
-给我一把枪  -我有好几把
- I need a gun. - I have several.
弗莱一直是泰特复仇大计的一部分
Frye's always been a part of Tate's game.
炸弹  电话  我猜想马可也是
The bomb, the phone calls. I'm guessing Marco is, too.
我不予置评
I'm not gonn comment on that.
一旦找到弗莱  这里就没你的事了
Hey, we found Frye, we're done here.
副队长  我能跟你一起去吗
Lieutenant, can I come with you?
-为了弗莱还是报道  -都有
- What, for Frye or the story? - For both.
-不行  你会妨碍警方办案的  -拜托
- No. You'll be in the way. - Please.
随你吧
Aw, hell.
搞什么  他妈的到底搞什么
What the hell's going... what the hell's going on?
你知道的  丹尼尔  你马上就要没命了
You know, Daniel. This is the end of your life.
放他走  这是你我之间的恩怨
Let him go. This is between you and I!
丹尼尔也牵涉其中  脱不了干系  不是吗
Oh, Daniel is a part of it. A big part, aren't you, Daniel?
-你疯了  泰特  -也许吧
- You're crazy, Tate. - Maybe.
你只要说出真相
But all you had to do was tell the truth.
记者就是这样的  但你却没做到
That's what a journalist does, but you didn't do that.
你俩都给我过去
Over there, both of you.
快点  快点
Come on. Come on
最重要的就是将那两个人救下来
This is all about getting those two men off the bridge alive.
明白了吗
Do you understand that?
-明白  -好
- Yes. - Good.
那就老实待着  别碍我的事
Then keep your mouth shut and stay out of my way.
我有正经事要做
I got a job to do.
-他提出什么要求了吗  -目前没有
- He made any demands yet? - Not yet.
-狙击手就位了吗  -是的
- Got snipers in position? - Yes.
-很好  能瞄准吗  -是的  长官
- Good. You got a shot? - Yes, sir
我的炸药一旦引爆
If this vest I'm wearing detonates,
你  我  弗莱  还有这座桥的主体
it'll tear apart me, you, Frye
都会灰飞烟灭
and most of the center of the bridge.
好吧  戴维  你是老大
Okay, you're in control, David
-已经瞄准  只等您下令  -不  等等
- I've got a shot. On your call. - No, hang-hang on.
炸弹已经激活  让狙击手待命
Bomb's live. Have your sniper stand down.
他已经激活了炸药
He's activated the dead man's switch.
-不许开火  -不许开火
- Hold your fire. - Hold your fire
他裹了炸药  现在他说了算
He's engaged the vest. He is in control now.
现在什么情况
What's happening?
事情很不乐观
There is no good outcome here.
只能两败俱伤
None.
我的拇指扣动扳机  我们就全玩完
My thumb comes off this trigger, we all die.
你也永远别想救格斯了
And so does any hope of saving Gus.
只要你告诉儿子的下落  你想干什么都行
Just do whateve you have to do and tell me where my son is!
别再玩这些该死的游戏了
And-and stop with all thes bullshit games.
拿出你的枪
Take out your gun.
很好  现在瞄准他
Good. Now point it at him.
他在搞什么鬼
What the hell's he doing?
-马可  -丹尼尔
- Mar... - Daniel.
你的儿子命在旦夕了  马可
Your son is dying, Marco, right now
现在你还有选择
You have a choice to make.
我儿子在哪儿
Where is my son?
想想后果  马可
Consequences, Marco.
丹尼尔・弗莱这个人渣死了
Daniel Frye, a waste of a human being dies,
你的儿子就能活下来
your son lives.
我想大部分父亲都会愿意一试的
I think most fathers would take that bet.
也许你得进监狱
Then maybe you'd go to jail.
不过要是在华瑞兹  你未必会蹲牢子
Maybe it's Juarez, and they look the other way.
但总之你救回了你的儿子  他活下来了
But you have your son, and life goes on for him.
现在杀了他
Now, kill him.
我不会这么做的
I'm not gonna do that!
杀了他  就能救格斯
Kill him, save Gus.
不要
No.
-格斯快要死了  马可  -我...
- Gus is dying, Marco. - I'm...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
丹尼尔  告诉他你都干了什么
Daniel, tell him what you did.
我不是故意的
I didn't mean to.
那只是场意外
It was... it was a mistake.
你没有站出来  丹尼尔
You failed to act, Daniel
你什么都没做
You did nothing.
所以希望鲁伊斯警探能比你好点
Let's hope Detective Ruiz is made of better stuff.
怎么回事
Wha...
我不会这么做的
I'm not gonna do this!
他不正是你所憎恶的一切吗
Isn't he everything you hate, anyway?
就是因为他们华瑞兹才充斥着暴力
The reason your real Juarez is overrun with violence?
他们为了一己之欲来这里购买毒品
This... this is the man who buys those drugs
却完全漠视这片土地上发生的一切
and then sneers at the place he got them from
和无数死去的生命
and the people who died so he can pack his nose!
你在拖延时间
You're stalling right now.
我怎么知道我儿子还活着
How do I know my son is still alive?
你只能选择相信我
You're just gonna have to trust me.
毙了这满嘴谎言的家伙  我们就完事了
Now, shoot this lying piece of shit, and we'll be done.
我跟你不一样
I'm not like you.
你这样救不了任何人
You're not saving anyone.
丹尼尔
Daniel!
我们已经搜查过了
We've searched this already.
这里什么都没有  桑娅
There's nothing here, Sonya.
帮帮我
Help me.
停下  停下  我来
Stop it, stop it. I got it.
-怎么了  这里什么都没有
- What? There's nothing.
-墙灰  -老天
- Plaster. - Jesus.
拉出来  快点
Pull it out. All the way out. Come on.
好了  小心
All right, watch out.
站开点
Step back.
这本应该是高尚的行为吗
Was that supposed to be the honorable move?
但却只能显示你的懦弱
'Cause it was the cowardly one.
说明不了什么
It doesn't mean anything.
告诉我他在哪里
Just tell me where he is.
你很快就会像我一样
You will be like me before this ends.
我可以向你保证这点
That I can promise you.
我知道四周都包围了狙击手
In seconds, the snipers that I know are posted everywhere
很快他们就会向我开枪
wil take my head right off.
你就再也不会知道格斯的下落
And you'll never know where gus is.
不 不 别开枪  别开枪
No, no, no don't shoot. Don't shoot!
别开枪
Don't shoot!
大家都别开枪
Nobody shoot.
叫你的手下别开火
Have your men hold their fire.
不要开枪  不要开枪
Hold your fire, hold your fire.
格斯
Gus!
把枪拣起来  马可
Pick up the gun, Marco.
不拣吗
No?
你不是什么英雄
You're no hero.
阿尔玛跟我说了你和那女人干的好事
Alma told me what you did with that woman.
闭嘴
Oh, shut up!
你一点都没变
You haven't changed a bit.
你的欲望摧毁了一切
Your appetites ruin everything.
破坏了家庭和别人的生活
Destroy families, ruin lives
这一切都只是因为你想爽一炮吗
All so you can get your rock off?
求你了  告诉我他在哪里
Just, please, tell m where he is.
他在一个黑暗的地方  马可
He's in a dark place, Marco.
一个冰冷  黑暗的地方
A cold, dark place.
很好  马可
Good, Marco.
很好
Good.
你知道迦勒是怎么死的吗
Do you know how Caleb died,
严格来说
technically?
他是在自己的血里被淹死的
He drowned in his own blood.
结束这一切吧  戴维
End this, David.
否则我会的
Or I will.
迦勒的肺被撞坏了  就在那边
Caleb's lungs were crushed, right over there.
救护车是五分钟后到的
Ambulance came in five minutes.
吉尔压根都没用上
It didn't even matter for Jill.
你知道那种感觉吗  马可
Do you have any idea what that's like, Marco?
失去一切的感觉
To lose everything.
失去你的妻子  儿子
Your wife, your son?
你不知道
No, you don't know.
你无法知道  马可
You can't know, Marco,
接到那个电话时的心情
what it's like to get that call.
还有亲眼去看他们
And to go see them.
我说了我很抱歉
I said I was sorry.
求你了
Please..
告诉我他在哪里
tell me where he is.
好吧
Okay.
-我需要跟马可谈谈  -桑娅
- I need to talk to Marco. - Sonya.
我得阻止他
I gotta stop him
没事  让她去
It's okay; leave it.
桑娅  小心
Sonya, be careful!
我儿子在哪里
Where is my son?
格斯已经死了  马可
Gus is dead, Marco.
马可  不要开枪
Marco! Don't shoot!
桑娅
Sonya?
桑娅  你找到他了吗
So... Sonya, did you find him?
他已经死了  马可
He's dead, Marco.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你有机会救他的  但是已经晚了
You had your chance to save him, but it's too late.
桑娅
Sonya!
马可  看着我  格斯已经死了
Marco, look at me. Gus is dead.
桑娅
Sonya!
他等着你去救他
He died in a cold, dark place,
却死在了那个冰冷黑暗的地方
waiting for you to rescue him.
现在你能做的只有一件事
And now there's only one thing left for you to do.
我找到他了
I found him!
我找到格斯了
I found Gus!
她在说谎
She's lying.
他在那栋房子里
He was in the house.
什么房子  桑娅
What house, Sonya?
钱伯斯的房子  他就在墙后面
Chambers' house. He was behind the wall.
他还活着吗
Did you find him alive?
把枪放下  马可
Put the gun down, Marco.
回答我
Answer me.
我儿子还活着吗
Is my son alive?
活着
Yes!
她不太会说谎  对吧
She's not a very good liar, is she?
桑娅
Sonya?
别杀他  马可
Don't kill him, Marco.
那正是他所希望的
That's what he wants you to do.
桑娅
Sonya?
求你了
Please!
我儿子要是活着就告诉我
Just tell me if my son is alive.
他还活着
Yes!
你找到他了
You found him...
但他还活着吗
but is he alive?
活着
Yes.
还活着
Yes!
桑娅
Sonya...
求你了
please tell me...
告诉我真相
tell me the truth.
我们去医院把你的手腕复位吧
What do you say we go to that hospital and get the wrist set?
好吧
Okay.
你冲到桥上去了
You went out on the bridge.
很可能被杀死
You could've got yoursel killed.
我觉得这是最正确的选择
I did what I thought was best.
如果是你  会怎么做呢  汉克
What... what would you have done, Hank.
我真不知道我会怎么做
I can't honestly say what I would have done.
马可可能会杀了泰特
Marco would have killed Tate.
有可能
Yes, he would.
而你阻止了他
And you prevented that.
我不知道该跟他说什么
I don't know what to say to him.
去看看他
Just go see him.
他现在正需要朋友
He could use a friend right now.
朋友
A friend?
走吧
Go on.
我给你带了些衣服
I brought you some clothes.
干吗
What for?
你出院的时候穿
When you get out.
我不希望你在这里  桑娅
I don't want you here, Sonya.
听我说  马可
I need you to listen to me, Marco.
我不希望你在这里  请出去
你听我说完我就走
I'm not leaving until you listen to me.
我尽力去救格斯了
I tried my best to save Gus,
但他当时已经死了
but he was already dead.
我对你说的
And I told you...
就是你想听到的
what you wanted to hear.
不然我该怎么做呢
What was I supposed to do?
你就
Just..
让我自己待会儿  拜托了
leave me alone, please.
我不会走的
I'm not leaving.
我们是朋友  马可
We're friends, Marco.
我只不过是照着你说的做
And I only did what you taught me,
是朋友都会这么做
friends would do for each other.
朋友
Friends?
是啊
Yes.
你阻止我开枪杀他
You stopped me from shooting him.
为什么
Why?
因为那正是他所希望的
Because that's what he wanted.
而你不是那种人
And you're not that person.
不  我正是那种人
Oh, no. Yeah, I am that person.
我们不是朋友  桑娅
We're not friends, Sonya.
我们曾是搭档
We were partners.
现在不是了
That's over.
好吧
Okay.
好
我不想再提起这件事了
Now I don't want to talk about this anymore.
我只想  一个人待着
I just... want to be alone.
好吧
Okay.
好
走啊  快走啊
Go! Just go!
弗莱  丹尼尔・弗莱
Frye. Daniel Frye.
你是家属吗
Are you family?
不是
No.
很抱歉  你不能看他
I'm sorry you can't see him.
拜托你了
Please.
他没什么朋友
He doesn't have a lot of friends.
好吧
All right.
情况很糟  对吧
It's bad, isn't it.
目前还不清楚
We won't know for a while.
摔得挺重的
It was quite a fall.
他会好起来吗
Is he gonna be all right?
他身上有严重的内部创伤
He suffered massive internal injury,
脑部伤和脊椎外伤
brain and spine trauma.
什么时候能知道结果
When will we know?
这要取决于接下来的四十八个小时了
We'll have to see how he does over the next 48 hours.
我们就只能干等吗
So we just wait?
目前来说  是的
For now, yes.
停尸房
有事吗
Can I help you?
我想要见一见我的儿子
I'd like to see my son.
古斯塔沃・鲁伊斯
Gustavo Ruiz.
没问题
Of course.
格斯・鲁伊斯
送达医院已经死亡